groups.im 2009-12-02

# Policy of Privacy | groups.im - We host Group Chat on Instant Messengers! (Windows Live Messenger / MSN, Yahoo Messenger)

## Policy of Privacy

ABOUT GROUPS.IM PRIVACY

groups.im takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

This policy covers how groups.im treats personal information that groups.im collects and receives, including information related to your past use of groups.im products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This privacy policy only applies to groups.im. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that groups.im does not own or control, or to people that groups.im does not employ or manage. In addition, some companies that groups.im has acquired have their own, preexisting privacy policies which may be viewed on our acquired companies page.

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

groups.im collects personal information when you register with groups.im, when you use groups.im products or services, when you visit groups.im pages or the pages of certain groups.im partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. groups.im may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we might also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. When you register with groups.im and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

groups.im collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

groups.im automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, groups.im cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

groups.im uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

User Profile information such as user id is displayed to groups.im members in order to facilitate user interaction in the groups.im social networking community. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, groups.im allows users to search for other members and groups. groups.im.com displays little personal information in order to keep a safe and secure environment for all groups.im members.

From time to time, groups.im or a partner of groups.im, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstakes, or contest on groups.im. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address, home address, and/or answer certain questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

As otherwise described in this privacy statement, groups.im will not disclose any personal information to a third party, except if any situation arises and groups.im believes disclosure is necessary. The following are exceptions:

1\. groups.im will conform to any legal requirements, respond to a subpoena, search warrant or any other legal process received, whether or not a response is required by applicable law

2\. groups.im also reserves the right to exchange any personal information to any related companies.

3\. groups.im will enforce the groups.im "Terms of Service" to protect our rights; and to protect the safety of members of the public and users of groups.im.com

4\. groups.im reserves the right to transfer personal information to any successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of groups.im or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.

COOKIES

groups.im may set and access groups.im cookies on your computer.

groups.im lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to groups.im cookies.

groups.im uses web beacons to access groups.im cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with groups.im products and services.

CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with regulations to protect personal information about you.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

groups.im may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your groups.im account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us: http://feedback.groups.im/ .
